techgage.com 2019-08-12

# Privacy Policy – Techgage

### Techgage Privacy Policy

As an advocate of the consumer, Techgage understands its role to protect the personal information of our visitors. We never require you to give us personal information in order to enjoy the content on our site. You can even post in our forums without registering, in threads that are dedicated to comments about specific site articles. Our philosophy is one of minimalism when it comes to collecting your information for any purpose – we try not to ask for any more information than we absolutely need.

 **Personal Information**  
‘Personal information’ is defined as the following:  
Name  
Address  
Telephone number(s)  
Date of birth  
Occupation  
Personal Interests

We never collect personal information on our site that is not provided voluntarily. Any personal information we collect from you is treated as confidential, and is not shared with any third party except as required by law. Some personal information is required for forum membership; however, this information is stored in an encrypted database and is used only for verification purposes – we need to be sure that you are an actual person and not a machine or a commercial entity. Your IP address may be automatically logged by our site, however this is never used to trace you personally except where a potential violation of our Terms and Conditions of Use or Forum Rules is concerned. Techgage Networks, Inc. uses Google Analytics in conjunctions with Google Adsense, which includes remarketing information, and demographics and interests reports. To Opt-out of adsense targeted ads, you can follow the guide by Google [here](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/142293?hl=en-GB), and opt-out of Analytics tracking [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

 **Information We Will Never Request**  
Techgage staff will never ask you for your forum password, so you should never provide it. We will never ask for any financial information from you such as your credit card number, social security number, or bank account number. Should you be asked for financial information by a person who claims to be affiliated with Techgage Networks, Inc., do not provide it.

 **Disclosure**  
Under no circumstances will Techgage Networks, Inc. sell or provide your personal information to a third party, with the exception of state, local, and federal law enforcement agencies as required by law.

 **Advertisers**  
Some of our advertisers use browser ‘cookies’ to track your browsing, however no personal information is collected by our advertisers. Instead, our advertisers collect ‘usage’ data – what ads you click on and what ads you’ve already seen multiple times, in order to best target their marketing efforts. (Ad revenue is what keeps Techgage going.)

 **Affiliate Marketing**  
Techgage Networks, Inc. is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

 **Mailings**  
Users who are on one of our mailing lists may opt-out at any time; unsubscription information is provided at the bottom of all list emails.
